Let's look at the tree tree So somewhere
Давайте посмотрим древо древо Так где-то
I even had this with UNESCO by the way
у меня даже было это с ЮНЕСКО кстати
you can look at UNESCO tree tree
можете посмотреть в ЮНЕСКО древо древо
tree tree UNESCO Yes yes yes this is UNESCO in
древо ЮНЕСКО Да да да это Юнеско в
UNESCO
ЮНЕСКО
That was Ancient Russian from Russian
стоит Вот был Древне русский с русского
went Ukrainian and
пошёл украинский и
Belarusian tree Good evening
белорусский Добрый вечер
Great evening Good evening I'm from  Ukraine, the city of
Здорово вечер Добрый Я из Украины город
Khmelnitsky You are
Хмельницкий Вы
from
откуда
Russia and the
Россия а
city is the Moscow
город Московская
region under the Moscow castle In short, it
область под моско замка короче да
turns out, well, it doesn’t matter in
получается ну неважно в
principle, well, if you’re interested, I can
принципе ну если интересует могу
Smolensk SN this is the Slensk region and not the
Смоленск СН сэто сленска область а не
Moscow kimet, everything belongs to Moscow
Московская кимет все к Москве относятся
Well, it’s not like this, the city of Smolensk,
Ну это не как это город Смоленск
Smolensk region, administrative
Смоленской области административный
center Well, you  why is it Irma is not the
центр Ну вам зачем это Ирма это не
Moscow
Московская
region I say near Moscow they call it
область Я говорю под Москвой называют
the Moscow region And how many kilometers is it still
Подмосковье А сколько километров это ещё
considered the Moscow region Well listen to the
считается Подмосковье Ну слушайте на
territory of Russia you know
территорию территории России знаете
How many thousands of kimets yes That’s why I
Сколь тысяч киме да Вот я поэтому я у
ask everyone how many kimets from Moscow 300
всех спрашиваю ско кимет с москов 300
500 700 I think maybe about  thousands like
500 700 я я думаю может около тысячи вот
that and thousands That is, it turns out that
так вот а тысячи То есть получается
Latvia is the Moscow region somewhere. Yes,
Латвия - это Подмосковье где-то Да ну
look, to Latvia it’s 1,000
смотрите до Латвии 1.000
km. Well, no, look from Moscow to Ukraine,
км Ну нет смотрите от Москвы до Украины
how many kilometers? Well, from Moscow to St.
сколько километров Ну от Москвы до
Petersburg, how many there are? 700 no, what do you
Питера сколько там 700 нет что вы до
think it’s to St. Petersburg? Well, St. Petersburg, Moscow region
Питера считаете Ну Питер Подмосковье
turns out
получается
yes Well, that’s what I said My assessments Well, yes,
да Ну я так Свои оценки сказал Ну так да
according to your assessments, St. Petersburg is a
по вашим оценкам Питер - это Подмосковье
cool suburb of Moscow. Oh well, Russia is the
прикольно [__] Ну так и россия-то
only one, what’s the difference? No, yes, Russia is
одна какая разница Не ну а да Россия
alone; there are many Moscow suburbs; the Russian
одна Подмосковье много Российская
Federation is not a member of any St.
Федерация она не состоит с каких-то
Petersburg or Moscow; that’s all  a single
Питер или Москва это всё единое
state and what does it
государство а из чего Она
consist of? From the Federation With With Which there are a
состоит с Федерации С С какой очень
lot of look if we have more than 198
много смотрите если у нас больше 198 там
nationalities somewhere,
где-то национальности да
then we love everyone. It
то мы Всех любим Неважно кто они буряты
doesn’t matter who they are Buryats. It doesn’t matter who they are Chechens or others or the
Неважно кто они чеченцы или другие или
fifth tenth or Kotino Balkari o val
пятый десятый или котино балкари о ва
lyut Well  everyone also thinks well If you
лют Ну все тоже думают хорошо Если вы их
love them, why are you sending them to die in a
любите зачем вы их отправляете умирать в
foreign
чужую
country, so no one controls them, they do it
страну так никто не управляет их они
themselves, but where is there voluntary mobilization,
сами дово да где добровольно мобилизация
yes, look, the Chechens also
же есть есть да смотрите чеченцы тоже
voluntarily went. Well, yes,
добровольно пошли Ну да добровольно
Kadyrov asked voluntarily, he says, Let’s go
Кадыров типа попросил говорит Давайте
there, Who is there Dobrova all  - so I, I,
там Кто там Доброва вс-таки я я я
yes, well, if in Ukraine there are no movements,
да ну если в Украине нету каких движений
there are no levers, then you mean
нету каких рычагов значит вы значит у
you have nothing.
вас ничего не по Просто
You’re just boring, you’re not boring, there’s some question, you’re
скучны вы не скучны есть какой-то вопрос
serious, let’s ask me some
серьёзны давай задам мне какой-то
interesting question so that I’m
интересный вопрос чтобы я ж
provocative against I don’t know  what should I
провокационный противо не знаю что м
ask
задать
against How do you How do you fold your hands or
противо Как вы Как вы руки сложите или
how do you sweat your hands up When this year
как руки поте вверх Когда в этом году
or next
или в следующем
year we
году мы
do
сделаем
Uh-huh koche when when they come to you you
Угу коче когда когда к вам придут вы
will sleep correctly No no Or
будете спать правильно Нет нет Или
will you rest we will sit in the pose of the
будете отдыхать мы будем сидеть в позе
master of life and  look at your nothingness
хозяин на жизни и смотреть на ваше ничто
existence And who does this Cool,
существование А кто такое делает Классно
I rolled with you with my hands, there really is
я тебя у катался с руками правда есть
at least one country that
есть хоть одна страна которая что-нибудь
can do something Can harm
могу Может навредить
Russia one country,
России одну страну
call Iran
зовите Иран
China So we are together with Russia, and the
Китай Так мы вместе с Россией причём
kitan of
китан
Russia, look, let's see which country
Росси смотри давайте так какая страна
blew up the Northern  the flow to you
взорвала Северный поток вам
America can harm you maybe which
Америка может навредить вам может какая
country blew up the Crimean
страна взорвала вам Крымский
bridge for you I think America together with Ukraine
мост Я думаю Америка вместе с Украиной
Well, Ukraine wouldn’t pull all this, yes, that
Ну Украина не Потянула бы это всё да то
is, look weak you can
есть смотрите слабенький вам можно
blow up the whole world is watching you blow up the
взорвать весь мир смотрит вам взорвали
Nord Stream through which you pumped
Северный поток через который вы качали
money And you have nothing  were able to do And
бабло И вы ничего не смогли сделать И
that we didn’t pump the money Nord Stream
что не мы не качали бабло Северный поток
2 It hasn’t worked yet, they blew it up, they
второй Он ещ не работал е взорвали
wanted to pump it up, they didn’t blow it up, those wires were
хотели качать не взорвали те проводы
only pumped through Ukraine, I’m still
чтоб только через Украину качают до сих
pumping it through Ukraine. Yes, and in short,
пор качаю через Украину Да и сри короче
they blew up your property, which means
вам взорвали ваше имущество зна значит
you’re being scammed through
вы значит вас разводят через Украину
Poland is pumping gas into Ukraine The most
качают газ Польша Больше всех
gas was received from Russia, but Poland received the most gas from
получила с России вот газ больше всего с
Russia and is selling it to Ukraine
России получила Польша и продают Украине
at twice the price, look. Well, we are an
в два раза дороже смотри Ну мы мы
American puppet. I understand. And you
американская марионетка Понятно А вы
get it, the Americans blew up the
получается вам американцы взорвали
Nord Stream and you swallow no, we are not
Северный поток и вы глотну нет мы не
a puppet, we supply that is  if
марионетка мы поставляем то есть если у
we have a product, we’re not a puppet,
нас есть продукт не мы марионетка
look, we’re a puppet of America, that’s
смотрите мы марионетка Америки это же
clear. And you It turns out that who is
понятно А вы Получается кто раб раб
America’s slave, America’s slave to you, America blew up the Nord
Америки вам Америка взорвала Северный
Stream and you, uh, washed your face and moved on. No,
поток и вы ээ умылись и пошли дальше Нет
that’s then Europe, a puppet. Well, it’s
это тогда Европа марионетка Ну это
Europe that was blown up, not in Russia,
Европе взорвали не в России
it’s not in Russia.  blew up No, well, who
это не в России взорвали Да не ну кому
blew it up blew up in Europe so that
это взорвали взорвали в Европе чтоб
Nord Stream was Nord Stream Whose
Северный поток был Северный поток Чей
was the general system this is Germany Germany
был об общее стро это Германия Германия
there are a lot of companies investing
там очень много компании влаживать
money Nord Stream 2 Nord Stream About
деньги Северный поток 2 Северный поток О
this
это имущество
Gazprom property was not divided there already
Газпрома не там поделено было уже
Nord Stream 2 Nord Stream 2  and
Северный поток 2 Северный поток 2 и
which one is
какой
it or through that one? It doesn’t matter. It’s
это или через ту нету Как не важно Это
important that Chain was blown up. The
важно тот что взорвали Чейн
Nord Stream was blown up for the second time.
был Северный поток второй раз взорвали
It was German and Russian. In short, there’s
он было немецкое с российской короче вам
no damage to you from this,
вам ущерба никакого от этого нет
yes. No, we would sell from us. Here
да Как нету мы бы продавали от нас Вот
you have damage, damage, damage.  and
вам есть ущерб ущерб ущерб есть и
Germany there is damage and America has caused
Германия ущерб есть а Америка нанесла
damage to you and you are silent
вам ущерб и вы молчите
Yes America can do anything to you
Да Америка может делать с вами что
because you are against you are against
угодно потому что вы против вы против
America Nobody no no well in general uh what
Америки Никто нет нет ну в общем э что
did we do against America in he China
мы сделали против Америки в он Китай
America China Russia and Belarus brought in
Америка Китай Россия и Белоруссия внесли
to investigate  this is
чтобы расследовали это
all you guys will investigate
всё всё вы терпилы будете расследовать
you didn’t blow up America anything all the countries
вы не взорвали Америки ничего все страны
rejected even Germany
отклонили даже Германию
and they showed you that you Patience a question for
да вам показали что вы Терпи вопрос к
you question who blew up then Nord
вам вопрос кто взорвал тогда Северный
Stream you can say it’s Russia Ukraine
поток можете сказать это Россия Украина
Ari the Americans blew up the Americans And
Ари американцы вот американцы взорвали А
why on And why did they say on Ukraine
почему на А почему на Украину сказали
it was the Ukrainians because look
это украинцы были потому что смотрите
Zelensky asked Biden Can we
Зеленский попросил байдена Можно мы
say that it’s us because we want
скажем что это мы потому что мы хотим
Zan that we’re cool
Зан что мы крутые
That is, you’re not cool We’re cool And you’re
То есть вы терпилы не Мы крутые А вы
crazy they blew you up, not that is, they
терпилы вам же взорвали не то есть вам
tell you Yeah, we blew up the Nord Stream
говорят Ага Северный поток взорвали мы
Well, like, you’ll be patient  and say that it
Ну типа вы Потерпите и скажите что это
was you and all this you mean since Ukraine
вы были и всё это вы значите пор Украина
won from the explosion of the Nord Stream,
выиграла от взрыва Северного потока
well, Ukraine won What is pumping
выиграла Ну Украина выиграла Что качает
gas, look Why why do you call it
газ смотрите Почему почему вы называете
war then If you pump gas, then if you are this is
тогда войной Если вы качаете газ значит
not a war, a special operation is not a
если вы это не война спецоперация это не
war, this is a special operation you you  war is
война это спецоперация вас вас война это
this a special operation for which there was a war
это спецоперация у на что была война
someone declared war No who declared
кто-то объявлял войну Нет кто объявлял
war what are you delusional What kind of war
войну что Ты бредишь Какая война
special operation there was no declaration of war You mean there
спецоперация не было объявления войны Ты
was no war yes Well don’t call it howl it’s a
что войны не было да Ну так не называе
special operation
спецоперация
war what did you take that this is a war if  if there was
война что ты взял что это война если бы
a war, We would have already bombed your
война Мы разбомбили уже вашу
Moscow and whose Crimea is then
Москву а чей Крым тогда
Ukrainian and Donbass is Ukrainian and
украинский а Донбасс украинский а
Novorossiya Novorossiya is the fruit of your
новороссия Новорос это плод ваших
fantasies, okay why
фантазий ладно почему
not I won’t stand, you know, look Novoross
нет не выстою знаете смотрите Новорос
after the victory of Ukraine a
после победы Украины будет
separate region of Novorossiya will be made with the
сделан отдельный регион новороссия с
center in Novorossiysk, you already have
центром в Новороссийске есть же уже
such a city Novorossiysk  ok
такой город у вас Новороссийск ладно
ok ok part of the Krasnodar region
ладно ладно часть Краснодарского края
it will be Novoro So don’t you confuse the
это будет Новоро Так вы не не путайте
cities there, there is also
там города там тоже
something else and Krasnodar it will be part of
есть ещ что а Краснодар это будет часть
Novorossiya we will make Novorossiysk
новоросси мы сделаем вот Новороссийская
will be a people’s
будет народная
republic This is who understands the Tatars will not be
республика Это кто поним татары будут не
f or the Poles to the
ф или поляки
French you
францу вы
fields You are already in Polish  language You say
поля Вы уже на польском языке Говорите
you understand that there is a railway so that
понимаете то есть ЖД чтобы опять туркам
Crimea goes back to the Turks correctly No tour to the Turks
отошёл Крым правильно Нет турм туркам от
goes to Anapa and
идёт Анапа и
Sochi Crimea to whom Crimea to Ukraine yes
Сочи Крым кому Крым Украине да
hello
здравствуйте
Yes And why did the Turks divide Cyprus so
Да А почему турки вот Кипр разделили так
well it’s a pain for themselves And now
вот хорошо для себя само боль А теперь
Anapa will be divided Oh well They’re coming in and  the
Анапу разделят Да ладно Они же входят а
Turks
турки
are entering the Poles
входят поляки
will take Smolensk for themselves you, by the way,
возьмут Смоленск себе вы вы же кстати
speak Polish You speak Polish
по-польски Говорите У вас же польский
You are not this Polish language this is an adverb of the
Вы не это польский язык это это наречие
Polish language no you know the tree of the
польского языка нет вы знаете древо
Russian language look you speak
русского языка это смотрите вы говорите
now the Russian language was not when before the
сейчас не русский язык был когда до
revolution when Lenin was  there were also letters
революции когда Ленин был ещё там буквы
yat you are now writing
ять были вы сейчас пишете
in the Polish language about the World Cup you say well
нак польского языка о ЧМ вы говорите ну
look Lenin whenever
смотрите Ленин когда бы
you write in Russian Lenin was not a tsar
Вы писали на русском языке Ленин царм не
Lenin was not when he was When there was a
был не Ленин вот когда ещ был Когда был
tsar then Len Lenin was the same
царь тогда Лен Ленин был тот же самый
as here for example I am not  I say that Lenin
как вот например я не говорю что Ленин
was a tsar, look No, you said Lenin
был царь смотри Нет ты сказал Ленин цар
was a tsar, I said Lenin When there was a tsar, that’s
был я сказал Ленин Когда был царь вот
when there was a tsar And Lenin understood the time of the
когда был царь И был Ленин понял время
Russian Empire, you wrote the initial letter in
Российская империя писали Вы буквица
old Russians, then when Lenin came
старыми русскими потом когда Ленин прил
to power, he annulled and issued a decree on the
к вла аннулировал и выдал декрет о
Polish language, do you remember the decree  about the land
польском языке помнишь он декрет о земле
a decree on time and a decree on the Polish
декрет о времени и декрет о польском
language that the language will now be in the Russian
языке что язык теперь будет в Российской
in the Russian Republic Yes, it
в Российской республике Да она там
will be called Polish there Yes and that’s why
называлась будет польский Да и поэтому у
you threw out these old Russian
вас выкинули старые вот эти русские
letters yat no, you have the letters yat they
буквы ять нету же у вас буквы ять
threw out the letter and with a dot Yes and  so,
выкинули букву и с точечка Да и поэтому
uh, they started speaking in dialect, they just
ээ стали говорить на наречие просто
adapted the alphabet, and under uh, there
адаптировали алфавит да под ээ букв
were more letters before, but there were fewer of them.
раньше же было больше стало меньше Да
Moreover, these writers of yours fought
ещё ваши эти литераторы они боролись
to keep the letter e. Lenin. It’s just that he was
чтобы букву ё оставили Ленин Просто он
when he was in Germany. Yes, and in Poland, I
же когда был в Германии Да и в Польше я
seemed to live a lot for Him.
бы как бы очень много жил Ему
I liked the Polish language, he
понравилось именно польский язык он
says that the Polish language should be,
говорит что польский язык должен быть
as it were, united for all Slavs,
как бы объединённый для всех славян так
and since then, uh, you have no Russian language
и с тех пор ээ у вас русского языка не
left, the Polish language has become, but
осталось стал польский язык но осталась
the letter e remained and by the way they wanted to destroy it,
буква ё и её хотели кстати уничтожить
so the letter e was written like that, too.
так букву ё писали вот как е тоже было
remember this, and then they returned it
же такое помните а потом вернули
after all, that it is necessary to revive the Ancient
всё-таки что надо возрождать Древний
language, and they returned the letter e Yes, but
язык да и букву е вернули Да но всё
still, it remains Polish. You see,
равно у вас он остаётся польский
it’s a little spoiled by
Понимаете вот немножко испорченный
various dialects there, Turkic
разными наречиями там тюркскими
Udmurt, yes, you forget that in the half of
удмуртски да вы вы забываете что в полу
Ukraine there was Austria-Hungary Yes  we are now
Украины было австро-венгрия Да мы сечас
in Austro-Hungarian Yes, you think
на австро-венгерского Да вот вы думаете
Austro Wenger we speak Austro-Hungarian
Австро Венгер мы на австро-венгерского
Yes And you are in
говорим Да А вы на
Polish Moscow belonged Moscow
польском Москва ж принадлежала Москва
belonged to Poland
принадлежала Польше
belonged to you think to Poland Moscow
принадлежала вы думаете Польше Москва
belonged to Poland and then you
принадлежала Польше да потом у вас у вас
had the Maidan when you had  I also
Был Майдан ском го Когда у вас был я ещё
say the same thing when you had the Maidan
то же говорю когда у вас Был Майдан
of Minin and Pozharsky, you rebelled against the
Минина и Пожарского вы восстали против
legitimate ruler of Poland, yes, you
законного правителя польского да у вас
had the Maidan and they threw everything away, so
Был Майдан да и всё и скинули поэтому
Poland has all the rights to Moscow,
Польша имеет все права на Москву язык у
your language is still Polish. Well, that
вас до сих пор польский остался Да ну то
is, you are imperials  if you are friends with the Poles
есть вы имперцы если вы с поляками
or you are a Pole then no Well
дружите или вы поляк значит нет Ну
look we are not we are the Austro-Hungarian
смотри не мы мы австро-венгерской
imperials we have the Austro-Hungarian language yes
имперцы у нас австро-венгерской язык да
you have Polish because you were under
у вас польский потому что вы были под
Poland we are under the Austro-Hungary no
Польшей мы под австро-венгрией нет
wait something you are confusing look
подождите что-то вы путаете смотрите
let’s Austro  - let’s take Hungary, we were,
Давайте австро-венгрию возьмём мы были
look, we were under Austro-Hungary,
смотрите мы были под австро-венгрией у
we still have the Austro-Hungarian
нас до сих пор идёт австро-венгерской
language, it’s just in Cyrillic and
язык просто его на кириллицу и
is called Ukrainian. You have the Polish
называется украинский У вас же польский
language, they just translated it into
язык просто тоже перевели его на
Cyrillic and called it like ru. You communicate
кириллицы и назвали типа ру Вы общаетесь
in Russian.  Now I’m talking to you in
на русском языке Вот сейчас я с вами на
Polish, it’s the Polish language, it’s
польском говорю это же польский язык это
not the Polish language, it’s the Polish language. You
не польский язык это польский язык Вы
were in Poland once, you were in Poland
были в Польше когда-то вы были в Польше
in They are exactly the same. They speak only with
во Они же точно так же Говорят только у
them and write in Latin, you write in
них и пишут латиницей вы пишете
Cyrillic, absolutely the same, same  the language is
кириллицей абсолютно тот же тот же язык
a little spoiled, your words are spoiled and the
немножко у вас испорченные слова и
proclamation is a little spoiled,
испорченное провозглашение есть немножко
well then Poland
ну тогда Польша неправильно
speaks incorrectly correctly now Paul, you
разговаривает правильно сейчас Поль вы
speak incorrectly. For example, the Poles
неправильно Говорите например поляки
say chi and you speak
говорят чи а вы говорите
ches and look at you because of that. That's
чес и смотрите у вас из-за того Вот
why your spelling is incorrect, you
почему у вас неправильное написание вы
write milk and you read milk  the
пишете молоко а читаете молоко
language has deteriorated, you understand Paul In
испортился язык понимаете Поль В
Polish it was written milk in Ancient Polish
польском было в Древне польском молоко
Yes, and in Ukrainian now there is
писалось Да и в украинском сейчас
milk left in Austro-Hungarian And you
осталось в австро-венгерской молоко А вы
read milk or the word You speak it and
читаете молоко или слово Говорите его а
write
пишете
it And you say
его А говорите
exactly what this is old You know
так вот именно что это старый вы знаете
the tree of languages ​​Yes the tree is the tree  from
древо вот языков Да древо древо из
Polish everything is
польского все
Slavic all Slavic tree you
славянски все славянские древо вы
looked at the tree all Slavic languages
смотрели древо все славянские языки
came from Polish
пошли из польского
we will and then block me correctly I wo
будем а потом мне заблокируйте правильно
n’t block I won’t block my hands Look raised
не не заблокирую я руки Смотри поднял Ну
Well, you’ll raise my hands then I’ll Because there are a
вот мне руки поднимете потом я Потому
lot of people like this that you present, yes, look now  I'll
много да вот смотрите сейчас я сейчас
go away now and here's the tree Let's look at the
отойду и вот древо Давайте посмотрим
tree tree So somewhere I even had
древо древо Так где-то у меня даже было
this with UNESCO by the way you can look at
это с ЮНЕСКО кстати можете посмотреть в
UNESCO tree tree tree UNESCO yes yes Yes,
ЮНЕСКО древо древо древо ЮНЕСКО да да Да
this is UNESCO in UNESCO
это Юнеско в ЮНЕСКО
It was Ancient Russian from Russian
стоит Вот был Древне русский с русского
went Ukrainian and the tree uh Belarusian
пошёл украинский и древо ээ белорусски
tree tree tree
древо древо древо
Show it like this Hands
Покажите так Руки
Up now I’m a little Look at this,
Вверх сейчас я немножко Вот посмотри это
okay So what, I see a picture from
ладно Так и что я вижу картинку из
some children’s No, this is a fairy tale
какого-то Нет это дей сказки
So where is it written that there are
Так где там где там написано что там
Russians Well,
русские Ну
show the Russian language there L Ukrainian
покажите русский язык там Л украинский
So you look here  Russian Well, this is
Так вы смотрите вот русский Ну это
just a picture of a tree, an owl, an owl sitting
просто картинка дерева сова Сова сидит
on a
на
tree, this is a UNESCO drawing of
дереве это ЮНЕСКО рисовала
this owl there, this is a UNESCO owl, an owl was drawn by a
эту там сова это ЮНЕСКО сову нарисовал
tree, I Tai, I will now show you the tree too.
древо я Тай Я сейчас вам древо тоже
like somehow
как каким-то образом
Old Russian yes Or
древнерусским да Или
somehow so where did I come from I’ll
каким-то так откуда пошёл я сейчас
look now Look now the tree I’ll show
посмотрю Смотри сейчас древо я покажу
Polish Polish Polish Polish where
польский польский польский польский где
it’s Polish Yes, they mixed the
он польский язык Да там намешали же
Polish language there and interfered with it Austrian
польский язык на мешали это австри
Wenger was then occupied it was
Венгер была потом занимали это ж было
there and Lithuanian  look at this
там и Литовской вот смотри вот это вот
tree, okay, what is there, what is
это древо Да ладно А что А что там А что
there flying there, let's zoom in
там летают там ну давай увелич
on something, chickens are flying or something, these are
на там что-то курицы летают что ли Это
balls, they're chickens, come on, come on,
шарики они куриц Давай Давай по давай
let's zoom in, zoom in, zoom in, I'll
давай увеличи увеличи увеличи я я тоже
see too, or there will be an owl  stand or a rooster
посмо или сова будет стоять или петух
there, I don’t know, I’ll be interested, yes, I’ll
там я не знаю мне будет интересно да я
look, I’ll enlarge it. Why
посмотрю увеличу А что она не увеличится
won’t it increase? Yes, Kornichkovsky, something doesn’t
Да корнич ковский что-то не
increase. Well, let’s
увеличивается оно Ну да давай куда
ask where to ask what I’m going to do. Let’s
задать что я Давай у себя
take a look at my place. Yes, Google it. Korney
посмотрю возьми да в Google Корней
Chukovsky, the fairy-tale
Чуковский сказочное
tree of roots.  write in Russian or Korney
древо корней по-русски писать или Корней
Chukovsky Yes
Чуковский Да
in Russian Korney
по-русски Корней
Chukovsky Chukovsky Yes fairytale
Чуковский Чуковский Да сказочное
tree fairytale tree Well, interesting
древо сказочное древо ну интересно
in general fairytale miracle of the tree miracle of the tree And
вообще сказочный чудо древа чудо древа А
well, that miracle of the tree Korney Chukovsky is already fabulous The miracle of the tree
ну сказочно уже ту чудо древа корне
is a fairy tale
Чуковский Чудо древа это сказка
something Well, not this tree of
что-то Ну не это древо
languages ​​is not Well, listen, well  I’m already kidding
языков не Ну слушай ну уже прикалываюсь
here, it’s
тут разводняк
some kind of scam, but you can look
какой-то но можно посмотреть
by the way, it’s interesting, the miracle tree
кстати интересно чудо древо
Well, what is
Ну о чём
it about, fairy tales,
оно сказки
fairy tales Well, that is, you don’t know history,
сказки Ну то есть историю вы не знаете
but probably
да наверное
your own. Dude, you don’t really know Chukovsky,
свою Чувак ты корне Чуковского не знаешь
I was born in 1981. You
я восемьдесят первого года рождения Ты
also lived under the Union. Yes, I did.  already old,
же при Союзе тоже жил Да я уже старый
just, what are you talking about,
просто ну ты что ковского
of course not, it fits in the root of Chukovsky
Конечно нет вписывает корне Чуковский
Miracle
Чудо
tree So it highlighted okay, let's have a
древо Так высветило ладно давайте
real tree, come on, come on, let's have a
настоящее древо давай давай давай давай
tree of languages, then
древо языков потом ещё про бандеру
you'll tell us about Bandera from others there,
расскажешь по других там
yes, come on, show
да да давай покажи
me, forget it, 2018,
мне вот забей 2018 год
request Ukrainian language, wait,
запрос украинский язык подожди
how are you  you think In what century did the
а как ты думаешь В каком веке появился
Ukrainian language appear wait wait wait
украинский язык подожди подожди подожди
I’ll show you the tree now no need the
я тебе сейчас древо покажу да не надо
tree they’ve already forgotten about already look at the tree you
древо уже забыли про уже смотри древо
see the tree Well there too Do you have an owl or
видишь древо Ну там тоже У тебя сова или
not Yes, well, the tree is
нет Да ну древо
mine Well, as mine I showed you the same thing
свой Ну как свой я то же самое тебе
not mine  it’s not the same, well, it’s not the
показал свой не не то же самое ну как не
same Why so far
тоже самое Почему пока сво ещё раз у
you didn’t have such a tree again Well, okay, are you
тебя не такое древо было Ну ладно Ты что
kidding me or what, I took it from the UNESCO website
прикалываешься что ли я с сайта ЮНЕСКО
Well, don’t remove it now,
взял Ну вот ты сейчас не убирай его
let me wonder, or did you
давай мне ж интересно ну или вы
change it, so I showed it  yours
переделали вот я показал своё
Just wait, which side is Sava
Вот подожди у тебя Сава с какого Бока
standing on the right or left? Well, my camera
стоит справа или слева Ну у меня камера
displays it on the right, will it be on your left
отображает она справо будет у тебя слева
or on the right? Well, look below
или как спра Да ну так смотри внизу у
what you have written on the
тебя что там написано на
stratis, it’s written below on mine Now
стратис у меня внизу написано Сейчас
wait
подожди
East Yes on the stratis later
Восточно Да на стратис потом
West then India right right above the owl
Западно потом Индия прям прямо над совой
what is written right above it Russian No
что написано прямо над собой русский Нет
there is Ukrainian
там украинский
written no below Ukrainian sweats
написано нет ниже украинский поты Ты с
What site did you get the tree from this
какого ты с какого сайта взял древо это
you redrawn the tree Well look how you
вы перерисовали древо Ну посмотри как
look Here I am showing you here I
смотри Вот я показываю тебе вот я тебе
showed you from what site  while
показал вот с какого сайта пока ВМ сайте
you found the VM site Well, look, let's do it this way. Enlarge
ты нашёл Ну смотри Давай так ты Увеличь
mine. I'll look at yours or yours, God forbid.
свой я посмотрю у тебя или у тебя не дай
Well, I'll be interested. Give me yours. Show me.
Бог Ну я мне будет интересно Давай сво
First, show me from which site
Покажи Сначала покажи с какого сайта
it's not Show me from which site. Which
нежи не Покажи с какого сайта А значит
means you're wrong, so I'm right then I'm not  I
ошибка ты значишь я прав тогда не я
Tell you the name of the site from which you
Скажи название сайта с которого ты древо
downloaded the tree. Well, look. Go to Google.
скачал Ну вот смотри Заходишь в Google
So Throw it all in and
Так Закидываешь это всё и высвечивается
the picture is displayed. Show me. Exactly in Google, in
картинка Вот покажи Вот именно в Гугле в
Google, uh, where it was
Гугле ээ где оно
found. No, look, Yes, I throw it up on Google.
нашло Нет я смотри Да закидываю Google
So,
Так
tree of languages ​​UNESCO, so Yazykov tree
древо языков ЮНЕСКО так древо Языкова
UNESCO Yes, that’s right  or like Well, yes, yes, Yeah,
ЮНЕСКО Да правильно или как Ну да да
UNESCO and there are a lot of photos there for you,
ЮНЕСКО и там тебе очень много фото
namely, Face there is another one,
так а именно вот Face там другой пя де
here is this photo with a tree and
вот вот это фото с древом и свой как у
your website shows what is signed there,
тебя сайт показывает что там подписано
which site is under this
какой сайт под этим
UNESCO tree, Ukrainian language about And I
древом ЮНЕСКО украинский язык про А я
understand  now I now understand Look
понял теперь я теперь понял Посмотри что
what I understand those I'm beautiful
что я понял те я красавы
beautiful means UNESCO
красавы значит ЮНЕСКО
UNESCO the Ukrainian language comes from
ЮНЕСКО украинский язык произошёл от
Russian That's the
русского Вот вот
whole tree this is a tree What is your website
всё древо это да древо Какой у тебя сайт
below written a little Look here
внизу написанный чуть-чуть Смотри вот
right under the picture here what what
прямо под картинкой вот тут что что у
you have written Here
тебя пишет Вот
here is jal.com
тут jal.com
some kind of UNESCO Ukrainian language Well,
какой-то ЮНЕСКО украинский язык Ну сам
look for yourself what you are so worried about there.
посмотри что ты паришься там так Ты
Look at this picture like where I have it,
смотри это картинка типа отку вот у меня
for example, look, there is a picture
например смотри есть вот картинка
presentation in short In short, in short, they are already
презентация на короче Короче короче уже
making such a mistake that the Ukrainian language is
так разводят что украинский язык э
my picture I’m not not not  leaders, I’m
картинка свой я не не не вожди я
already absolutely beautiful, look again,
уже это вообще красава смотри ещё раз
this is this tree from a fairy tale, so
вот это это дерево со сказочки так
every teacher paints it in his own way
каждый учитель разрисовывает по-своему
Here’s another fairy tale, look, here’s
Вот ещё сказочка вот смотри вот
another UNESCO rejoiced in short there, yes yes yes And
ещё ЮНЕСКО ликовал короче там да да да А
as for the Ukrainian language, I also agree
насчёт украинского языка тоже согласен
that there are not enough words there, no words
что там ну слов не хватает слов не
enough doesn’t reach the Russian language
хватает не дотягивает до Русского языка
yes yes seriously Come on let’s
да да серьёзно Давай давай с юном
sort it out with the young man wait you scored
разберёмся подожди ты забил
Russian Ukrainian language prol from Russian No no there is
рус украинский язык прол от русс Нет
nothing like this for a
нету такого вот с
while dude some
поре чувак дерево какой-то учитель
Russian language teacher took a tree and drew words on this
русского языка взял нарисовал На этом
tree Are you so UNESCO
дереве слова Ты что так это ЮНЕСКО
wrote this  Well, we didn’t write
написал это ж не мы написали
Yes, that means the Russian language according to the Ukrainian
Да значит русский язык по от украинского
rule
прави
as UNESCO saté Find this Okay,
как сате ЮНЕСКО такое Найди Хорошо давай
let’s go through history No, let’s talk about the
давай по истори пройдём Нет давай про
words you said Oles Kuzina was that
слова ты сказал Олесь Кузина был что
Oles Buzina Oles Buzina was not this is not
Олесь Бузина Олеся бузина не было это не
Oles Buzina this is fiction as fiction
Олесь Бузина это вымысел как вымысел
Show me on  on the UNESCO website Olesya
Покажи мне на сайте ЮНЕСКО Олеся
Elder so they killed him 201 don’t show it on the
бузину так он его убили 201 не покажи на
UNESCO website until the fifteenth year Olesya
сайте ЮНЕСКО до пятнадцатого года Олеся
Elder was not on the site But what do you
бузину на сайте его не было Но а что ты
think was wrong there was no Buzi again and
думаешь не прав не было бузи ещё раз е
no Olesya Elder was not there he was killed this is a
нету Олесь Бузина не было его убили это
fictional literary character And mom
персонаж литературный вымышлены А мама
was and mom was and mom was the President of
был а мама была а мама был это президент
America Dale Ales Ales elder - It
Америки Дале Алесь Алесь бузина - Это
was a literary
был литературный
character you just sell yes damn it’s
персонаж вы просто даж да блин это вот
like the Strugatsky Brothers had a character Yes what are
как у Братьев Стругацких был персонаж Да
you talking about as Osta Bender There was Asta
ты о чём как оста Бендер Вот был Аста
Bender look again he was like this Where is it  have
Бендер смотри ещё раз был такой Где это
you seen this elderberry live? Oles
вы видели этого бузину вживую Олесь
elderberry Yes, why not show him?
бузину Да почему е показать его
Let me read his poem. My
давай прочитаю его стих Мой самый
favorite poem is that right, look, it’s
любимый стих это правильно смотрите это
just like Pinocchio. Let me
ж так же как буратина сти Давай я
read the poem, it’s very good. There was no
прочитаю стих очень хороший не было не
elderberry. It’s fiction. It’s a character.
было бузины это вымысел это персонаж да
and people didn’t
Ну конечно ну блин а люди что его не
see him You saw Elderberry of course live
видели Вы видели бузину конечно вживую
Yes once where did you see
Да один раз где Вы видели
him in Crimea I saw him once so it
его в крму Видел один раз так это не
wasn’t Elderberry but who was it so let them
бузина был да кто это был так пусть оны
not exist Yes look I’ll read
не существует Да вот смотрите я прочитаю
his verse And you will find him let’s cry
его стих А вы найдёте его дай плач
Ukraine cry, you are your own traitor and
Украина плачь ты сама себе предатель и
executioner, you crushed with your own hand
палач ты своею собственной рукой
Reason and peace, you kill the best
задавила Разум и покой убиваешь лучших
sons of Ratu, and on the evil ones and biting like a
сыновей Рату и на злобных и кусая как
snake on its own tail, you created your own
змея сама себе за хвост создала своих
limit, the Holocaust, this elderberry - This is
предела холокост вот этот бузину - Это
a real one, not on the site, show it on the
настоящий не на сайте покажите на сайте
UNESCO website, there is a verse  on the
ЮНЕСКО есть стих на сайте
UNESCO website Yes Listen, I wrote 10 books, eight
ЮНЕСКО Да Слушай написал 10 книг восемь
books I wrote, I’ll read Show me at least one
книг написал прочитаю Покажите хоть одну
book on the UNESCO website you
книгу на сайте ЮНЕСКО древо вы мне
showed me the tree on the UNESCO website Show me the
показали на сайте ЮНЕСКО Покажите
book Yes, I can not only show
книгу Да я могу не только на сайте
it on the USCO website on the UNESCO website I
юско его показать на сайте ЮНЕСКО я
showed the UNESCO tree You know what
показал древо ЮНЕСКО Вы знаете что такое
UNESCO is  what is there again there is Show
ЮНЕСКО что есть ещё раз есть Покажите
me the elderberry on the tree there is the elderberry on the tree
мне бузину на древе есть бузина на древе
on the UNESCO website
на сайте ЮНЕСКО
you om you you take the writer And what is Pushkin
вы ом вы вы берёте писателя А что Пушкин
on the UNESCO tree or what are you talking about
есть на древе ЮНЕСКО что ли Вы о
where he is there then what look And what is
чём где он там есть то что смотри А что
Shevchenko Is on the tree with  Yes, Putin
Шевченко Есть на древе уне с Да Путина ж
was depicted on the UNESCO tree, there was
изобразили на древ ЮНЕСКО там же было о
also a green oak written by the onion and UNESCO
ещё написал у лука дуб зелёный и ЮНЕСКО
did the job, made Pushkin's oak. Why are
сдела сдела сделала дуб Пушкина Да что
you
вы
breeding for now? Show me, let's not be
разводите пока Покажите мне бу давай не
without sarcasm. Let's go ahead. You're just kidding me.
без сарказма Давайте Ты прикалываешься
I'm just pony, you're kidding me.
Просто я Поня водишь с меня ты
Budina is really Budin.  I saw
прикалывался Будина реально будин увидел
that in Ukraine everyone knows what
что в Украине каждый знает что
it is. Well, listen, well, they killed
это Ну слушай ну убили тоже так просто
a character just like that, but they didn’t kill a real
персонажа да та не убили реального
person, it was
человека это было
killing then the character is correct. So there
убивает тогда персонаж правильно Так не
was no real elderberry, there was no dude,
было реального бузины не было чувак Ты
why don’t you
что не опля
eat, they just took you and showed it to you,
ешь вам просто взяли показали тильку Да
okay, okay, okay  and others were there or
ладно ладно хорошо а а другие были или
not
нет
Which Well politicians Which who were killed
Какие Ну политиков Какие кого убили
Nemtsov I know Nemtsov
Немцова вот знаю Немцова
was killed him they were killed there in Russia I
убили нем убили там в России я за
speak for Ukraine and who was killed in Ukraine
Украину говорю а кого в Украине убили
le We figured it out It was a character there
ле Мы же разобрались Это был персонаж не
was no such person in reality there
было такого человека в реальности есть
You don’t agree that you  killed a
Вы не соглашаетесь что вас убили
man that two
человека что два
people if there was such Oles Buzina
человека если был такой Олесь Бузина
Show me the birth certificate
Покажите мне свидетельство о рождении
that the document that he was born is
что ведь документ что он родился
really a certificate of the birth of the
действительно свидетельство рождения
forest show
леса покажи
What UNESCO is about - This is a story you understand
О чём ЮНЕСКО - Это история понимаете
there is Show the family Show the
есть Покажите родовое Покажите
family tree of Oles Buzina and you
генеалогическое древо Олеся бузины и вы
will switch correctly
переключите правильно
No, so you read  his books on
Нет так вы по почитайте его книги по
Show read him Show watch
Покажите почитайте его Покажите смотрите
this the author took it in order to promote the
это автор взял для того чтобы раскрутить
books he invented this character there was no
книги придумал этого персонажа не было
Olesya the elderberry in reality is not a creature
Олеся бузины в реальности не существо
dude Let's show the video where he argued
чувак Давайте видео покажу где он спорил
with Zhirinovsky watch the video as you want
с Жириновским смотри видео како хочешь
you can
можешь
show the person there was no there
показать человека не было не было не
was no Ale  Who wrote and who wrote it in the
было Але Кто писал а кто писал его в
book ak and who wrote uh 12 chairs who
книге ак а кто писал ээ 12 стульев кто
wrote Olesya Elderberry Here was the author was the author there
писал олежу бузина Вот был Был автор был
were no collections Olesya Elderberry wrote
автор коллек не было Олеся бузины писал
with about p yes the editors with 1 +1
с о п да редакция с 1 +1
wrote That’s me I damn it, I realized that
писала Вот это я Я блин вот я понял что
this is about
вот такую про вот
the Propaganda that you are conducting. This is
Пропаганду которую ты ведёшь Вот вот
real. Who can even trust you,
реально Кто тебе может вообще поверить
here is a person like a man. There lived a man in
вот человеку как человек Жил человек в
Kiev
Киеве
who is
который
actually a real Ukrainian. I
настоя настоящий украинец я тебе
showed you the tree. Show me the tree on
показывал древо Покажи мне Древо на
which there is Show me the tree on which there
котором есть Покажи мне Древо на котором
is Oles Elder Show me the
есть Олесь Бузина Покажи мне древо
UNESCO tree  on which there is Les elderberry and an
ЮНЕСКО на котором есть Лесь бузина и
owl, or at least an owl with an elderberry wasp without
сова или хотя бы сова с осем бузиной без
a tree Show it you want Do you want to know yes
древа Покажи ты хочешь Хочешь узнать да
And you see Khrushchev's tree Khrushchev so
А ты Хрущёва видишь древа Хрущёва так
Khrushchev was not there either and Khrushchev was not there either
Хрущёва не было тоже и Хрущёва тоже не
and Brezhnev was not there either
было не было И Брежнева тоже не было не
and Lenin was not there either  it wasn’t like that, the
было и Ленина тоже не было так СССР не
USSR wasn’t the USSR, it’s made up Well, that’s
было СССР это придуманный Ну ну
right, then your mother wasn’t there either,
правильно тогда мамы твоей тоже не было
not my mom is, but she was born in Ukraine
не мама моя есть но она в Украине
Oh well, yes, really,
родилась Да ладно Да реально
and your dad wasn’t there either was born in Ukraine,
а папы тоже твоего не было был в Украине
yes And there weren’t others How can you
родился да А других не было Как ты
prove that  The USSR existed Prove that the USSR
докажешь что СССР был Докажи что СССР
existed and your grandfather did not exist Well,
был а деда твого не было Ну в Украине
they all lived in Ukraine, you came up with a fairy tale about the
они все жили вам придумали сказку про
USSR, that the USSR was what year you were
СССР что был СССР какого года
born, What difference does it make to you, I’m already
рождения Да какая тебе разница я уже
old And you’re
старый А ты
young, if the USSR had what kind of helicopter and
молодой если ССР бы какие были вертол и
plane it
самол в
was in the USSR  helicopter in America
ССР какие были вертолёте в Америке
Of course
Конечно
I know we were what the game consoles were called
знаю были ми были как назвались игровые
airplanes What were the game consoles called in the SR
приставки самолёты Как назывались в СР
And what were the
игровые приставки А как назывались
game consoles called in America in you see you
игровые приставки в Америки в видишь ты
don’t know I understood And I know because
не знаешь я понял А я знаю потому
with the USSR America was always ahead and
что с ССР был впереди всегда Америке а
then they started flirting
потом они начали заигрывать
with  SS The first ones in space gathered for the sake of the first one
у СС Первые в космос собрали ради первое
in
в
space, look, it’s good if this USSR was
космос смотри хорошо если этот СССР был
so cool Why did it fall apart and
такой крутой Почему ж он развалился и
Russia now And that Gagarin didn’t happen, it did
Россия сейчас А что Гагарина не было так
n’t happen Well, okay, it didn’t happen, and the Americans
не было Ну ладно не было да американцы
didn’t land on the moon either, well, it’s just a
также на луну Не высаживались ну это ж
fake, the
фейк
Russians just came up with it  the myth about
просто русские придумали миф про
Gagarin and about the Soviet Union, the Americans
Гагарина и про Советский Союз американцы
came up with about Armstrong Ila and you
придумали про Армстронга Илу а ты
think that it was all in vain Well,
думаешь что это всё зря было Ну а как
look, where is there any evidence
смотри Где какие-то есть доказательства
that Gagarin flew into space, that he even
Что Гагарин летал в космос что он вообще
existed, the whole world knows where
существовал весь мир это знает где
show it on the UNESCO website
покажите на сайте ЮНЕСКО
Show Show  Garina on the UNESCO website
Покажите Покажи Гарина на сайте ЮНЕСКО
So we Show Garina on the UNESCO website
Так мы Покажи Гарина на сайте ЮНЕСКО
Why didn’t you
Почему вы не
rule Gagarin existed Show him
прави ели Гагарин существовал Покажи его
on the UNESCO website
на сайте ЮНЕСКО
Younes this is it
юнес это оно
historically wait you confirmed you
исторически подожди ты подтвердил ты
said that that is, it turns out this is
сказал что то есть получается вот это
this tree Say yes, it turns out I have
вот это древо Сай да получается я име
something that is you
что то есть ты
showed, look, wait, you showed
показал смотри Подожди ты показал
nya, I now understand that you didn’t want to understand all the time
ня я тепер понял что ты всё время не
that the
хотел понять что
Ukrainian I understood you I want to
украинский я понял тебя Я тебе хол
tell you that
сказать что у
UNESCO is
ЮНЕСКО
really sick of it, it’s really just hard to blame
задолба реально просто жесть ко вин
began to the root of
начал корне
Chukovsky, subscribe to y Gra right away,
Чуковского подпишись на й Гра прям зараз
he’s doing
он а пок
it harder and harder  respectfully YouTube took us
це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня нас
through the ORV srg in your ban and there are so many
через срг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже багато
videos I don’t show people at all times I don’t show
вдео не показую людям вчасно не показуе
information about streams for this purpose for
информация про стримы тому для того щоб
Mali operational link to write
ми Мали оперативный звязок пишиться
directly at once and Popik there in telegra okm
прямо зараз а Попик там в телегра окм
video sche tezh tsikava and korisna information
видео ще теж цикава и корисна информация
and we are guilty  with you trima postiyny
и мы повинни з вами трима постийний
operational link
оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava ukraini pis
YouTube Слава украини пись